DAN KLEIN: So what do people actually
use these things for?
There's a limited industry for
Sudoku solvers, but CSPs are
used much more widely.
A big class of algorithms that people
use CSPs for are things like
assignment problems.
For example, if we wanted to figure out
who should teach what class based
on what classes they can teach.
Or a time tabling problem.
Which class should be offered
when and where.
You're all familiar with this problem
with your course scheduling.
Hardware configuration, layout,
things like that.
Factory scheduling, transportation
scheduling, fault
diagnosis in certain cases.
There are a lot of places where CSPs
are used in the real world, but the
machinery that solves them is going to
be the same general purpose stuff that
we're going to be talking about
today and next lecture.
Of course, in the real world, there
are lots of problems that involve
real-valued variables.
That either uses other techniques like
linear programming, or is discretized
before it's solved.